you're not GNA believe this but my robot
你不相信GNA 而是我的机器人
dog is finally alive wave to the
你们不是GNA所相信的... ...但我的机器人狗终于活过来了
最终狗狗终于 活着的浪潮到
dog is finally alive wave to the
audience would
最终狗狗终于成为 活着的浪潮观众会
听众将
audience would
you oh my gosh dude sit
观众,你能不能坐下? 哦,我的天哪 哥们,坐下
哦,我的天哪伙计,你坐下
you oh my gosh dude sit
down a I told you guys the top comment
哦,我的老天爷,坐下来 我告诉你们最顶尖的评论
我在下面跟你们说过 最顶尖的评论
down a I told you guys the top comment
would name it whatever you wanted with
一个我跟你们说过 最顶尖的评论会给它命名 无论你想用什么名字
无论你想用什么名字命名它
would name it whatever you wanted with
over 14,000 likes you guys picked boam f
随便你点什么名字 14000多人喜欢你们
超过14000人喜欢你们
over 14,000 likes you guys picked boam f
o a m now the only question I have for
超过14000人喜欢你们 选了一米牛排 现在我唯一要问的问题
现在我唯一要问的问题
o a m now the only question I have for
you guys now because I did in fact name
现在我唯一要问你们的问题了 因为我是实名
你们这些家伙,现在 因为我做了在事实上的名字
you guys now because I did in fact name
him foam what do you think foam should
你们这些家伙,现在 因为我确实给他取了名 泡沫,你们认为什么 泡沫应该
泡沫,你认为什么泡沫应该
him foam what do you think foam should
stand for and I wanted to see what he
你觉得泡沫应该代表什么 而我想看看他
站在我面前,我想看看他
stand for and I wanted to see what he
was actually capable so I took him in my
我想看看他的能力 所以我把他带进我的
其实我有能力,所以我把他带入我的身体
was actually capable so I took him in my
living room I pet him and then yeah I
我把他带到我的客厅 我抚摸他,然后是的
客厅,我抚摸他,然后是的
living room I pet him and then yeah I
kicked him okay but it was for science
客厅,我抚摸他,然后是的 我踢他好,踢他好,但这是科学的
踢他,踢他,还好,但这是科学的
kicked him okay but it was for science
then I pushed him but don't worry he's
踢踢他,但这是科学 之后我推他,但别担心他
然后我推他,但别担心他
then I pushed him but don't worry he's
fine he might even like it weirdly he's
然后我推他,但别担心他没事 他可能会觉得奇怪地喜欢他
他甚至可能喜欢 奇怪的他
fine he might even like it weirdly he's
way tougher than it looks but he's
他甚至可能觉得很奇怪 他比看起来要坚强得多 但是他...
比看起来要难得多 但他
way tougher than it looks but he's
probably plotting Revenge now I
比你看起来要难得多 但他现在可能正在密谋复仇
现在我可能正在策划复仇
probably plotting Revenge now I
introduced foam to my actual dog and
现在可能正在策划复仇... ...我把泡沫引入我的狗身上... ...
将泡沫引入我的真狗和
introduced foam to my actual dog and
that was a mistake apparently my dog
将泡沫引入我的真狗 而这显然是一个错误 我的狗
那显然是一个错误 我的狗
that was a mistake apparently my dog
thinks foam is a threat to National
很显然,我的狗认为泡沫对National是一种威胁
认为泡沫是对国家的威胁
thinks foam is a threat to National
Security I think my dog hates him but
我觉得我的狗讨厌他,但是...
保安我觉得我的狗恨他,但是...
Security I think my dog hates him but
honestly I kind of get it and then foam
保安我觉得我的狗恨他 但老实说,我得到它,然后泡沫
说实话,我得到了它,然后泡沫
honestly I kind of get it and then foam
tried to assert dominance by jumping at
坦白说,我得到了它,然后泡沫试图通过跳
试图通过跳跃来维护支配地位
tried to assert dominance by jumping at
her he can do so many different things
试图通过跳跃她来维护支配地位 他可以做很多不同的事情
她能做很多不同的事情
her he can do so many different things
like even climb but I haven't even tried
她可以做很多不同的事情 比如攀爬 但我还没试过
连爬也爬,但我还没试过
like even climb but I haven't even tried
that yet let me know what else in the
连爬都像攀爬一样 但我还没尝试过,但让我知道
但让我知道,在
that yet let me know what else in the
comments you want to see me do
但让我知道,在你的评论中,你还想看到我做什么
本字幕由AI大模型生成